<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R, Statistics and Visualization</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on R, Statistics and Visualization</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Linear Regression</title>
      <link>/2020/03/09/linear-regression/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/03/09/linear-regression/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Linear Regression is one of the most simple, intuitive, and widely used modeling technique which primarily predicts a quantitative response and thus falls under classification of Supervised Learning. A search on Google Scholar for the term “Linear Regression” returns 4+ million result and there are many good quality courses available online explaining Linear Regression for free. Today there are many sophisticated techniques available for predictive and prescriptive analytics but a solid foundation in Linear Regression is must to understand nuances of modeling before dealing with more advanced techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello World! My name is Vinay Singh and welcome to my website. I come from a Mechanical and Industrial Engineering background but lately found myself &amp;ldquo;playing&amp;rdquo; with lot of manufacturing data which got me hooked into Statistics using R. My plan is to keep my thoughts and code in one place using blogs, so primarily I&amp;rsquo;m writing this for my own benefit.
I dig Metallica and I ❤️ pipes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>